# **AMAR SHUKLA**

GURGAON, INDIA 7049066283 AMARSHUKLACS@GMAIL.COM

#### LINKEDIN

https://www.linkedin.com/in/amar-shukla01

## PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Software Developer having 2 years of experience working on development tasks and learning alongside. Experienced at working with customers, team members and project leaders to fulfill the requirements and deliver quality work within timelines. Always enthusiastic to enhance skills, grow personally and professionally and contribute towards the

#### **SKILLS**

- Python
- SQL
- Machine Learning
- Deep Learning

- Java
- SQL
- JavaScript
- React JS

## **WORK HISTORY**

AUGUST 2022 – PRESENT

Analyst | Deloitte | Hyderabad, India

AUGUST 2020 - JULY 2022

**Software Developer** | Amdocs | Gurgaon, India

Worked on a Project for A1, Bulgaria.

I was responsible for development and support to the project which deals with ordering, billing and customer management for telecom. I worked on react JS, redux and spring.

DECEMBER 2019 - APRIL 2020

Intern | Cognizant Technology Solutions | Bangalore, India

Completed C and Unix training.

OCTOBER 2019

City Coordinator | Progate

Organized hour of code for school students in association with

codechef, where they were introduced with python language.

AUGUST - NOVEMBER 2019

Campus Ambassador | IIT Delhi and IIM Rohtak

Organized and promoted events on campus related to these organizations.

## **EDUCATION**

SEPTEMBER 2020

**Bachelors of Engineering:** Computer Science Engineering Lakshmi Narain College Of Technology, Excellence, Bhopal Completed Bachelor's degree with aggregate of 8.6/10 CGPA

### **CERTIFICATIONS**

Programming. data structures and algorithms using Python: By NPTEL (IIT Madras)

Completed the certification with a consolidated score of 72%.

### **HOBBIES**

- Reading
- Writing
- Travelling